

Profile

Highly energetic & organized web developer leveraging my sales & marketing background to help in maximizing the user experience for all users on the web. With a recently earned full stack web developer certificate from Rutgers, State University of New Jersey, I have developed a number of skills in various programming languages (JS, HTML, CSS, JQuery) to help build a better experience on the web. I am excited to leverage my skills & education in a fast-paced environment where I can tackle projects & their challenges.

Employment History

Senior Account Manager at Choice Bank, Golden Valley, MN

January 2019 — August 2020

- Actively developing new business & expanding existing customer relationship through networking, tabling events, & visiting local businesses.
- Review products & services of existing clients to ensure they utilize all their services to help them maximize growth & success to their full potential.

Account Manager II at Venture/Choice Bank, Golden Valley, MN February 2017 — January 2019

- Managing new/existing book of business by conducting regular customer reviews to ensure my clients have all the products and services needed to maximize growth.
- Creating brand awareness in the community by attending local network events.
- Utilize social network to spread the word on local network events or seminars held at our offices.

Account Executive at Venture Bank, Golden Valley, MN

August 2015 — February 2017

- Providing exceptional service by working closely with bank officers to strengthen and expand core customer relationships while resolving client issues that arise to improve their business workflow & add efficiency.
- Promote deposit products & services to new/existing clients in order to help grow their business & ensure their financial business needs are met.
- Administer all deposit products & services using integrated banking programs, platforms, and software systems.

Sr. Customer Service Representative at Venture Bank, Bloomington, MN

February 2015 — August 2015

Details

6451 Pipewood Curve Excelsior MN, 55331 (763) 381-1383 vladimir.s.dimitrov14@gmail.com

Links

Skills

www.linkedin.com/in/vladimirsdimitrov https://github.com/Vlady14

Marketing
Customer Service
Microsoft Office
Microsoft Excel
Microsoft PowerPoint
B2B Sales
Marketing and Sales
Interpersonal Communication Skills
Leadership and Teamwork
Social Networking
Event Planning
JavaScript
jQuery
HTML & CSS
React.js
JSON
AJAX
Node.js
API
MySQL

- Respond promptly to our clients immediate needs related to transaction processing, online banking access & deposit account functionality & records.
- Use generalist knowledge to interact with and make appropriate referrals to both internal & external customers.
- Review all new accounts established to ensure they have been setup properly and all required documentation has been obtained.

Staffing Manager at Robert Half International - Accountemps, Bloomington, MN

February 2014 — September 2014

Personal & Small Business Banker II at Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., Eden Prairie, MN

January 2013 — February 2014

Personal Banker I at Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., Eden Prairie, MN February 2011 — January 2013

Customer Service & Sales Representative at Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., Excelsior, MN

November 2010 — February 2011

Bank Teller at Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., Excelsior, MN

July 2010 — November 2010

Customer Service Manager at Cub Foods, Shorewood, MN

April 2008 — February 2011

Bookkeeper/Cashier at Cub Foods, Shorewood, MN

October 2006 — April 2008

Education

Coding Bootcamp Certificate, Rutgers State University, Camden, NJ

October 2020 — January 2021

Full Stack Web Developer Program

Bachelors Degree in Marketing, Metropolitan State University, Saint Paul, MN

August 2014 — December 2016

General Education, Normandale Community College, Bloomington, MN

August 2008 — May 2014

1 References

References available upon request